(Leonard:)For the same reason I don't
wear the apron or the hair net.
(Sheldon:)Fine. What about epilepsy?
(Leonard:)I don't have epilepsy, either.
(Sheldon:)You don't,
but the surgeon might, hmm?
(Sheldon:)And your carotid artery is just
one shaky scalpel away
(Sheldon:)from becoming the dancing
fountain at Disneyland.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, do you realize that
driving is riskier than surgery?
(Sheldon:)I do. I have the drive
to the hospital right here.
(Sheldon:)That is if
you make it
(Sheldon:)to the car without
falling down the stairs.
(Sheldon:)And don't expect me to carry
you, I do that enough in life.
Buddy, I-I get that
you're worried about me
and I-I appreciate that,
but I'm not going to die.
(Sheldon:)You don't know that.
Well...
(Leonard:)I do know that it won't
be from an asteroid strike.
(Sheldon:)You know who else said that?
(Sheldon:)Every cocky T. rex
currently swimming around
(Sheldon:)in the gas tank of your car.
I-If there was
an asteroid strike,
(Leonard:)wouldn't you die, too?
(Sheldon:)I don't know--
I'm smart and scrappy,
(Sheldon:)I think I'd find a way.